Guide to the Cornell University News Service records, [ca. 1920s-2000s].
Cornell University News Service records
- Series VI. Cornell University News Services records, 1920s-2000s
  - Press Releases, News Clippings, Distribution Lists, Administrative Files, Subject Files
    - Alpha File Mostly 1980s
      - Agricultural Economics Press Releases, 1983-1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 33, Folder 18)
      - Agricultural Economics Press Releases, 1986-1989 (Box 4-3-15 - 33, Folder 19)
      - Agricultural Economics Clippings, 1985-1986 (Box 4-3-15 - 33, Folder 20)
      - Agricultural Economics Press Releases, 1980-1982 (Box 4-3-15 - 33, Folder 21)
      - Agriculture and Life Sciences Clippings, 1980 (Box 4-3-15 - 33, Folder 22)
      - Agriculture and Life Sciences Clippings, 1981 (Box 4-3-15 - 33, Folder 23)
      - Agriculture and Life Sciences Clippings, 1982 (Box 4-3-15 - 33, Folder 24)
      - Agriculture and Life Sciences Clippings, 1983 (Box 4-3-15 - 33, Folder 25)
      - Agriculture and Life Sciences Clippings, 1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 33, Folder 26)
      - Agriculture and Life Sciences Clippings, 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 33, Folder 27)
      - Agriculture and Life Sciences Clippings, 1986 (Box 4-3-15 - 33, Folder 28)
      - Agriculture and Life Sciences Clippings, 1986-1987 (Box 4-3-15 - 33, Folder 29)
      - Agriculture and Life Sciences Clippings, 1987 (Box 4-3-15 - 33, Folder 30)
      - Agriculture and Life Sciences Clippings, 1988 (Box 4-3-15 - 33, Folder 31)
      - Agriculture and Life Sciences Press Releases, 1980-1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 33, Folder 32)
      - Agriculture and Life Sciences Press Releases, 1986 (Box 4-3-15 - 33, Folder 33)
      - Agriculture and Life Sciences Press Releases, 1987 (Box 4-3-15 - 33, Folder 34)
      - Agriculture and Life Sciences Press Releases, 1988 (Box 4-3-15 - 33, Folder 35)
      - Agriculture and Life Sciences Press Releases, 1989 (Box 4-3-15 - 33, Folder 36)
      - Agronomy Press Releases, 1980-1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 33, Folder 37)
      - Agronomy Press Releases, 1985-1989 (Box 4-3-15 - 33, Folder 38)
      - Agriculture and Life Sciences Student Hometown News, 1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 33, Folder 39)
      - Animal Sciences Press Releases, 1980-1989 (Box 4-3-15 - 33, Folder 40)
      - Center for Applied Mathematics Press Releases and Clippings, 1985-1986 (Box 4-3-15 - 33, Folder 41)
      - Arts and Sciences Clippings, 1980-1988 (Box 4-3-15 - 33, Folder 42)
      - Arts and Sciences Press Releases, 1980-1989 (Box 4-3-15 - 33, Folder 43)
      - Arts and Sciences Press Releases, 1970-1979 (Box 4-3-15 - 33, Folder 44, 46)
      - Arts and Sciences Clippings, 1970-1979 (Box 4-3-15 - 33, Folder 45)
      - Commencement Press Releases, Clippings, Information, 1980 (Box 4-3-15 - 34, Folder 1)
      - Commencement Press Releases, Clippings, Information, 1981 (Box 4-3-15 - 34, Folder 2)
      - Commencement Press Releases, Clippings, Information, 1982 (Box 4-3-15 - 34, Folder 3)
      - Commencement Press Releases, Clippings, Information, 1983 (Box 4-3-15 - 34, Folder 4)
      - Commencement Press Releases, Clippings, Information, 1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 34, Folder 5)
      - Commencement Press Releases, Clippings, Information, 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 34, Folder 6)
      - Commencement Press Releases, Clippings, Information, 1986 (Box 4-3-15 - 34, Folder 7)
      - Commencement Press Releases, Clippings, Information, 1987 (Box 4-3-15 - 34, Folder 8)
      - Commencement Press Releases, Clippings, Information, 1988 (Box 4-3-15 - 34, Folder 9)
      - Commencement Press Releases, Clippings, Information, 1989 (Box 4-3-15 - 34, Folder 10)
      - Communications Art Department Clippings, 1981-1988 (Box 4-3-15 - 34, Folder 11)
      - Communications Art Department Background Information (Box 4-3-15 - 34, Folder 12)
      - Communications Art Department Press Releases, 1989 (Box 4-3-15 - 34, Folder 13)
      - Cooperative Extension Press Releases, 1987-1988 (Box 4-3-15 - 34, Folder 14)
      - Cooperative Extension Press Releases, 1989 (Box 4-3-15 - 34, Folder 15)
      - Cooperative Extension Clippings, 1984-1989 (Box 4-3-15 - 34, Folder 16)
      - Astronomy Press Releases, 1976, 1980-1989 (Box 4-3-15 - 34, Folder 17)
      - Astronomy: NASA photographs, 1976 (Box 4-3-15 - 34, Folder 18)
      - Biochemical Engineering Press Release, 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 34, Folder 19)
      - Consumer Economics and Housing Press Releases, 1980-1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 34, Folder 20)
      - Consumer Economics and Housing Press Releases, 1985-1986 (Box 4-3-15 - 34, Folder 21)
      - Cornell United Religious Works Press Releases, 1980-1989 (Box 4-3-15 - 34, Folder 22)
      - Cornell United Religious Works Clippings, 1980-1989 (Box 4-3-15 - 34, Folder 23)
      - Cornell United Religious Works Background Information, 1976-1980 (Box 4-3-15 - 34, Folder 24)
      - Design and Environmental Analysis Press Releases, 1980-1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 34, Folder 25)
      - Department of Education Clippings, 1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 34, Folder 26)
      - Department of Education Press Releases, 1980-1987 (Box 4-3-15 - 34, Folder 27)
      - College of Engineering Background Information, 1980-1988 (Box 4-3-15 - 34, Folder 28)
      - College of Engineering Press Releases, 1980-1989 (Box 4-3-15 - 34, Folder 29-30)
      - Entomology Information, 1980-1987 (Box 4-3-15 - 34, Folder 31)
      - Excellence Update Clippings, 1985-1986 (Box 4-3-15 - 34, Folder 32)
      - Fireworks Press Releases, 1979-1986 (Box 4-3-15 - 34, Folder 33)
      - Fireworks Clippings, 1979-1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 34, Folder 34)
      - Excellence Update Press Releases, 1985-1987 (Box 4-3-15 - 34, Folder 35)
      - Floriculture and Ornamental Horticulture Press Releases, 1980-1989 (Box 4-3-15 - 35, Folder 1-2)
      - Food Sciences Clippings, 1985-1989 (Box 4-3-15 - 35, Folder 3)
      - Food Sciences Press Releases, 1980-1989 (Box 4-3-15 - 35, Folder 4)
      - Garden Plot Press Releases and Clippings, 1980, 1986 (Box 4-3-15 - 35, Folder 5)
      - Gay Liberation Press Releases and Clippings, 1970-1983 (Box 4-3-15 - 35, Folder 6)
      - Geneva Experimental Station Press Releases, 1980-1989 (Box 4-3-15 - 35, Folder 7-8)
      - General Services Department Press Releases and Clippings, 1976-1983 (Box 4-3-15 - 35, Folder 9)
      - Hatch Act Press Releases, 1987 (Box 4-3-15 - 35, Folder 10)
      - Haitian Scholars Press Releases and Clippings, 1986 (Box 4-3-15 - 35, Folder 11)
      - Human Service Studies Press Releases, 1980-1982 (Box 4-3-15 - 35, Folder 12)
      - Human Service Studies Press Releases, 1983 (Box 4-3-15 - 35, Folder 13)
      - Human Service Studies Press Releases, 1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 35, Folder 14)
      - Human Service Studies Press Releases, 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 35, Folder 15)
      - Human Service Studies Press Releases, 1986 (Box 4-3-15 - 35, Folder 16)
      - Human Ecology Press Releases and Clippings, 1988-1990 (Box 4-3-15 - 35, Folder 17)
      - Identification Cards Press Releases, 1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 35, Folder 18)
      - Industrial and Labor Relations, 1980-1989 (Box 4-3-15 - 35, Folder 19)
      - Entrepreneur of the Year Program Information, Press Releases, Clippings, 1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 35, Folder 20-21)
      - Johnson Graduate School of Management Press Releases and Clippings, 1970-1979 (Box 4-3-15 - 35, Folder 22-23)
      - Johnson Graduate School of Management Press Releases and Clippings, 1980-1989 (Box 4-3-15 - 35, Folder 24-25)
      - Judicial Administration Clippings, 1969-1986 (Box 4-3-15 - 35, Folder 26)
      - Judicial Administration Press Releases, 1969-1986 (Box 4-3-15 - 35, Folder 27)
      - Law School Press Releases, 1972-1989 (Box 4-3-15 - 35, Folder 28)
      - Law School Information, 1932, 1964, 1970-1988 (Box 4-3-15 - 35, Folder 29)
      - Law School Clippings, 1976-1989 (Box 4-3-15 - 35, Folder 30)
      - Library Press Releases and Photographs, 1972-1989 (Box 4-3-15 - 35, Folder 31)
      - Library Background Information, 1972-1989 (Box 4-3-15 - 36, Folder 1)
      - Natural Resources Press Releases, 1980-1989 (Box 4-3-15 - 36, Folder 2)
      - Natural Resources Clippings, 1979, 1985-1989 (Box 4-3-15 - 36, Folder 3)
      - Library Clippings, 1972-1989 (Box 4-3-15 - 36, Folder 4)
      - Obituary Clippings and a Photograph, 1972-1989 (Box 4-3-15 - 36, Folder 5)
      - Ornithology Press Releases, 1980-1992 (Box 4-3-15 - 36, Folder 6)
      - Ornithology Clippings, 1968-1969 (Box 4-3-15 - 36, Folder 7)
      - Ornithology Clippings, 1971-1979 (Box 4-3-15 - 36, Folder 8)
      - Ornithology Clippings, 1980-1991 (Box 4-3-15 - 36, Folder 9)
      - Ornithology Miscellaneous, 1977-1988 (Box 4-3-15 - 36, Folder 10)
      - Plantations Press Releases, 1972-1989 (Box 4-3-15 - 36, Folder 11)
      - Plantations Clippings, 1982-1989 (Box 4-3-15 - 36, Folder 12)
      - Plantations Background Information, 1955, 1980-1987 (Box 4-3-15 - 36, Folder 13)
      - Plant Breeding Press Releases, 1980-1988 (Box 4-3-15 - 36, Folder 14)
      - Plant Pathology Press Releases, 1980-1989 (Box 4-3-15 - 36, Folder 15)
      - Plant Pathology Clippings, 1985-1989 (Box 4-3-15 - 36, Folder 16)
      - Public Safety Press Releases, 1980-1989 (Box 4-3-15 - 36, Folder 17)
      - Public Safety Clippings, 1980-1989 (Box 4-3-15 - 36, Folder 18)
      - Research Miscellaneous, 1984-1988 (Box 4-3-15 - 36, Folder 19)
      - Research Background Information, 1981-1988 (Box 4-3-15 - 36, Folder 20)
      - Research Press Releases, 1975-1989 (Box 4-3-15 - 36, Folder 21)
      - Research Clippings, 1973-1989 (Box 4-3-15 - 36, Folder 22)
      - Rhodes Speeches, 1977 (Box 4-3-15 - 37, Folder 1)
      - Rhodes Speeches, 1978 (Box 4-3-15 - 37, Folder 2)
      - Rhodes Speeches, 1979 (Box 4-3-15 - 37, Folder 3)
      - Rhodes Speeches, 1980 (Box 4-3-15 - 37, Folder 4)
      - Rhodes Speeches, 1981 (Box 4-3-15 - 37, Folder 5)
      - Rhodes Speeches, 1982 (Box 4-3-15 - 37, Folder 6)
      - Rhodes Speeches, 1983 (Box 4-3-15 - 37, Folder 7)
      - Rhodes Speeches, 1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 37, Folder 8)
      - Rhodes Speeches, 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 37, Folder 9)
      - Rhodes Speeches, 1986 (Box 4-3-15 - 37, Folder 10)
      - Rhodes Speeches, 1987 (Box 4-3-15 - 37, Folder 11)
      - Rhodes Speeches, 1988 (Box 4-3-15 - 37, Folder 12)
      - Rhodes Speeches, 1989 (Box 4-3-15 - 37, Folder 13)
      - Sardis Excavation Press Releases and Clippings, 1967-1968 (Box 4-3-15 - 37, Folder 14)
      - Stone Hall Press Releases, 1986 (Box 4-3-15 - 37, Folder 15)
      - Stone Hall Clippings, 1986 (Box 4-3-15 - 37, Folder 16)
      - Symposium Press Releases, 1980-1990 (Box 4-3-15 - 37, Folder 17)
      - Theory Center Clippings, 1988-1989 (Box 4-3-15 - 37, Folder 18)
      - Theory Center Press Releases and Clippings, 1985-1988 (Box 4-3-15 - 37, Folder 19-20)
      - Veterinary College 'Blue Ribbon Committee' Information, 1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 37, Folder 21)
      - Veterinary College Reports and Information, 1917, 1987-1989 (Box 4-3-15 - 37, Folder 22)
      - Veterinary College Press Releases, 1983-1987 (Box 4-3-15 - 37, Folder 23)
      - Veterinary College Background Information, 1954, 1978, 1986 (Box 4-3-15 - 37, Folder 24)
      - Veterinary College Clippings, 1980-1986 (Box 4-3-15 - 37, Folder 25)
      - Willsboro Research Development Farm Clippings, 1987 (Box 4-3-15 - 37, Folder 26)
      - WHCU Press Releases and Clippings, 1975, 1983-1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 37, Folder 27)
      - WSKG Press Releases and Clippings, 1988 (Box 4-3-15 - 37, Folder 28)
      - Zinck's Night Press Releases, 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 37, Folder 29)
    - Alpha Subject File, 1990s-2000s
      - Academic Programs and Planning, 1995-2001 (Box 4-3-15 - 99, Folder 1)
      - Admissions and Financial Aid (Box 4-3-15 - 99)
        - Admissions and Fin. Aid Enrollment - Clips, 1980s-1990s (Box 4-3-15 - 99, Folder 2)
        - Admissions and Fin. Aid Enrollment - Statistics, 1980s-1990s (Box 4-3-15 - 99, Folder 3)
        - Admissions and Fin. Aid Enrollment - Releases, 1973-2002 (Box 4-3-15 - 99, Folder 4)
        - Admissions and Fin. Aid Incoming Students, 1996-1998 (Box 4-3-15 - 99, Folder 5)
        - Admission and Financial Aid Registrar's Office, 1973-1995 (Box 4-3-15 - 99, Folder 6)
        - Admission and Financial Aid Tuition Releases, 1989-1996 (Box 4-3-15 - 99, Folder 7)
        - Admission and Financial Aid Tuition Clips, 1980-2004 (Box 4-3-15 - 99, Folder 8)
        - Admissions and Fin. Aid Undergraduates, 1995-1996 (Box 4-3-15 - 99, Folder 9)
        - Admissions and Financial Aid Clips, Prior to 1990 (Box 4-3-15 - 99, Folder 10)
        - Admissions and Financial Aid Releases, 1997-2002 (Box 4-3-15 - 99, Folder 11)
        - Admissions and Financial Aid Releases, 1995-1996 (Box 4-3-15 - 99, Folder 12)
        - Admissions and Financial Aid Releases, 1991-1994 (Box 4-3-15 - 99, Folder 13)
        - Admissions and Financial Aid Releases, Prior to 1990 (Box 4-3-15 - 99, Folder 14)
        - Admissions and Financial Aid Clips, 2002 (Box 4-3-15 - 99, Folder 15)
        - Admissions and Financial Aid Clips, 2000-2001 (Box 4-3-15 - 99, Folder 16)
        - Admissions and Financial Aid Clips, Releases 1998-1999 (Box 4-3-15 - 99, Folder 17)
        - Admissions and Financial Aid Clips, 1997 (Box 4-3-15 - 99, Folder 18)
        - Admissions and Financial Aid Clips, 1996 (Box 4-3-15 - 99, Folder 19)
        - Admissions and Financial Aid Clips, 1995 (Box 4-3-15 - 99, Folder 20)
        - Admissions and Financial Aid Clips, 1990-1994 (Box 4-3-15 - 99, Folder 21)
      - Africana Studies (Box 4-3-15 - 99)
        - Africana Studies Releases, 1997 (Box 4-3-15 - 99, Folder 22)
        - Africana Studies Releases, 1996 (Box 4-3-15 - 99, Folder 23)
        - Africana Studies Releases, 1995 (Box 4-3-15 - 99, Folder 24)
        - Africana Studies Releases, 1994 (Box 4-3-15 - 99, Folder 25)
        - Africana Studies Releases, 1990-1993 (Box 4-3-15 - 99, Folder 26)
        - Africana Studies Releases, Prior to 1990 (Box 4-3-15 - 99, Folder 27)
        - African Study and Research Center Clips, 1986-1999 (Box 4-3-15 - 99, Folder 28)
        - African Study and Research Center Clips, 2000 (Box 4-3-15 - 99, Folder 29)
      - Agriculture and Life Sciences (Box 4-3-15 - 99/100/101)
        - Agriculture and Life Sciences Releases, 2001 (Box 4-3-15 - 99, Folder 30)
        - Agriculture and Life Sciences Releases, 1999-2000 (Box 4-3-15 - 99, Folder 31)
        - Agriculture and Life Sciences - Animal Science Clips, 1990-2004 (Box 4-3-15 - 99, Folder 32)
        - Agriculture and Life Sciences - Clips, 2002 (Box 4-3-15 - 100, Folder 1)
        - Agriculture and Life Sciences - Clips, 2000-2001 (Box 4-3-15 - 100, Folder 2)
        - Agriculture and Life Sciences - Clips, 1995-1999 (Box 4-3-15 - 100, Folder 3)
        - Agriculture and Life Sciences - Clips, 1994 (Box 4-3-15 - 100, Folder 4)
        - Agriculture and Life Sciences - Clips, 1990-1996 (Box 4-3-15 - 100, Folder 5)
        - Agriculture and Life Sciences - Releases, 1997-1998 (Box 4-3-15 - 100, Folder 6)
        - Agriculture and Life Sciences - Releases, 1995-1996 (Box 4-3-15 - 100, Folder 7)
        - Agriculture and Life Sciences - Releases, 1993-1994 (Box 4-3-15 - 100, Folder 8)
        - Agriculture and Life Sciences - Releases, 1990-1992 (Box 4-3-15 - 100, Folder 9)
        - Agriculture and Life Sciences - Dean Search, 1994 (Box 4-3-15 - 100, Folder 10)
        - Agriculture and Life Sciences - Miscellaneous (Box 4-3-15 - 100, Folder 11)
        - Agricultural, Resource, and Managerial Econ Clips, 1995 (Box 4-3-15 - 100, Folder 12)
        - Agricultural, Resource, and Managerial Econ Clips, 1990-1994 (Box 4-3-15 - 100, Folder 13)
        - Agricultural, Resource, and Managerial Econ Releases, 1990-1994 (Box 4-3-15 - 100, Folder 14)
        - Agriculture and Life Sciences Clips and Releases, 1985-1995 (Box 4-3-15 - 100, Folder 15)
        - Agriculture and Life Sciences Agronomy (Box 4-3-15 - 100, Folder 16)
        - Alumni Association for CALS Clips, 1992-2004 (Box 4-3-15 - 100, Folder 17)
        - Alumni Association for CALS Releases, 1992-1999 (Box 4-3-15 - 100, Folder 18)
        - Agriculture and Life Sciences Animal Science Releases, 1988-2004 (Box 4-3-15 - 100, Folder 19)
        - Agriculture and Life Sciences Animal Science, Bovine Growth Hormone, 1981-1996 (Box 4-3-15 - 100, Folder 20)
        - Agriculture and Life Sciences Animal Science, Department of Poultry and Avian Sciences, 1980-1994 (Box 4-3-15 - 100, Folder 21)
        - Agriculture and Life Sciences, Biochemistry, Molecular and Cell Biology, 1995-1999 (Box 4-3-15 - 100, Folder 22)
        - Agriculture and Life Sciences, Biological Sciences, Div. of Clippings (Box 4-3-15 - 100, Folder 23)
        - Agriculture and Life Sciences, Biological Sciences Releases, 1994-1999 (Box 4-3-15 - 100, Folder 24)
        - Agriculture and Life Sciences, Biological Sciences, Div. of Releases, Prior to 1995 (Box 4-3-15 - 100, Folder 25)
        - Agriculture and Life Sciences, Biological Sciences, Div. of Miscellaneous, 1994-1999 (Box 4-3-15 - 100, Folder 26)
        - Agriculture and Life Sciences, Communication (Box 4-3-15 - 100, Folder 27)
        - ALS Community and Rural Development Institute Releases, 1994-2003 (Box 4-3-15 - 100, Folder 28)
        - ALS Community and Rural Development Institute Clips, 1994-2003 (Box 4-3-15 - 100, Folder 29)
        - ALS Community and Rural Development Institute Miscellaneous (Box 4-3-15 - 100, Folder 30)
        - ALS Cornell Eastern Europe Mexico (CEEM), 1998-2002 (Box 4-3-15 - 101, Folder 1)
        - ALS - Development Sociology (Box 4-3-15 - 101)
          - ALS Development Sociology Clips, 1991-2002 (Box 4-3-15 - 101, Folder 2)
          - ALS Development Sociology Clips, Prior to 1990 (Box 4-3-15 - 101, Folder 3)
          - ALS Development Sociology Releases, 1999-2004 (Box 4-3-15 - 101, Folder 4)
          - ALS Development Sociology Releases, 1994-1999 (Box 4-3-15 - 101, Folder 5)
          - ALS Development Sociology Releases, 1985-1993 (Box 4-3-15 - 101, Folder 6)
          - ALS Development Sociology Releases, 1980-1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 101, Folder 7)
          - ALS Development Sociology Farming Alternatives Program, 1995-1997 (Box 4-3-15 - 101, Folder 8)
        - ALS Ecology and Systematics Releases, 1971-2004 (Box 4-3-15 - 101, Folder 9)
        - ALS Ecology and Systematics Clips, 1972-2004 (Box 4-3-15 - 101, Folder 9)
        - ALS Ecology and Systematics Ecosystems Research Center, 1980-1990 (Box 4-3-15 - 101, Folder 10)
        - ALS Education Clips (Box 4-3-15 - 101, Folder 11)
        - ALS Education Releases, 1992-2003 (Box 4-3-15 - 101, Folder 12)
        - ALS Entomology Clips, 1998-2004 (Box 4-3-15 - 101, Folder 13)
        - ALS Entomology Clips, 1994-1997 (Box 4-3-15 - 101, Folder 14)
        - ALS Entomology Releases, 1998-2004 (Box 4-3-15 - 101, Folder 15)
        - ALS Entomology Releases, 1990-1997 (Box 4-3-15 - 101, Folder 16)
        - ALS Food Science Releases, 2001-2005 (Box 4-3-15 - 101, Folder 17)
        - ALS Food Science Releases, 2000 (Box 4-3-15 - 101, Folder 18)
        - ALS Food Science Releases, 1996-1999 (Box 4-3-15 - 101, Folder 19)
        - ALS Food Science Releases, 1994-1995 (Box 4-3-15 - 101, Folder 20)
        - ALS Food Science Clips, 1997-2004 (Box 4-3-15 - 101, Folder 21)
        - ALS Food Science Clips, 1990-1996 (Box 4-3-15 - 101, Folder 22)
        - ALS Section of Genetics and Development, 1986-2000 (Box 4-3-15 - 101, Folder 23)
        - ALS Hopkins Media Workshop, 2000 (Box 4-3-15 - 101, Folder 24)
        - ALS Floriculture and Ornamental Horticulture, Dutch Bulb Program, 1998 (Box 4-3-15 - 101, Folder 25)
        - ALS Floriculture and Ornamental Horticulture Releases, 1989-2003 (Box 4-3-15 - 101, Folder 26)
        - ALS Floriculture and Ornamental Horticulture Clips, 1989-2000 (Box 4-3-15 - 101, Folder 27)
        - ALS Fruit and Vegetable Science Clips, 1993-1999 (Box 4-3-15 - 101, Folder 28)
        - ALS Fruit and Vegetable Science Releases, 1992-1998 (Box 4-3-15 - 101, Folder 29)
        - ALS - Department of Natural Resources (Box 4-3-15 - 101)
          - ALS Natural Resources Releases, 2000-2003 (Box 4-3-15 - 101, Folder 30)
          - ALS Natural Resources Releases, 1995-1999 (Box 4-3-15 - 101, Folder 31)
          - ALS Natural Resources Releases, 1993-1994 (Box 4-3-15 - 101, Folder 32)
          - ALS Natural Resources Releases, 1990-1992 (Box 4-3-15 - 101, Folder 33)
          - ALS Natural Resources Clips, 2000-2004 (Box 4-3-15 - 101, Folder 34)
          - ALS Natural Resources Clips, 1995-1999 (Box 4-3-15 - 101, Folder 35)
          - ALS Natural Resources Clips, 1990-1994 (Box 4-3-15 - 101, Folder 36)
          - ALS Natural Resources Arnot Forest, 1994-2002 (Box 4-3-15 - 101, Folder 37)
        - ALS Rural Schools Program, 1994-1996 (Box 4-3-15 - 102, Folder 1)
        - ALS Soil, Crop, and ATM. Sciences, 1991-2004 (Box 4-3-15 - 102, Folder 2)
        - ALS Small Farms Program, 2004 (Box 4-3-15 - 102, Folder 3)
        - ALS USDA AG. Research Service, 1992-1997 (Box 4-3-15 - 102, Folder 4)
        - ALS Toxicology, 1988-1992 (Box 4-3-15 - 102, Folder 5)
        - Agricultural Health and Safety Program, 2004 (Box 4-3-15 - 107, Folder 12)
      - Greek Organizations, Fraternities, Clips, 1990s-2000s (Box 4-3-15 - 102, Folder 6)
      - Greek Organizations, Sororities, 1995-1996 (Box 4-3-15 - 102, Folder 7)
      - Greek Organizations, Clips, 1998-1999 (Box 4-3-15 - 102, Folder 8)
      - Greek Organizations, Releases, 1994-2002 (Box 4-3-15 - 102, Folder 9)
      - Greek Organizations, Fraternities, Releases, 1990-2004 (Box 4-3-15 - 102, Folder 10)
      - Greek Organizations, Assorted Papers, 1990s-2000s (Box 4-3-15 - 102, Folder 11)
      - Office of Alumni Affairs (Box 4-3-15 - 102)
        - Office of Alumni Affairs Clips, 1995-1998 (Box 4-3-15 - 102, Folder 12)
        - Office of Alumni Affairs Clips, 1990-1994 (Box 4-3-15 - 102, Folder 13)
        - Office of Alumni Affairs Releases, 2003-2004 (Box 4-3-15 - 102, Folder 14)
        - Office of Alumni Affairs Releases, 1996-2002 (Box 4-3-15 - 102, Folder 15)
        - Office of Alumni Affairs Releases, 1990-1995 (Box 4-3-15 - 102, Folder 15)
        - Office of Alumni Affairs Cornell Clubs, 1974-2000 (Box 4-3-15 - 102, Folder 16)
        - Office of Alumni Affairs Great Alumni Awards, 1994-1997 (Box 4-3-15 - 102, Folder 17)
        - Office of Alumni Affairs, Reunions Releases, 1998-2004 (Box 4-3-15 - 102, Folder 18)
        - Office of Alumni Affairs, Reunions Releases, 1985-1997 (Box 4-3-15 - 102, Folder 19)
        - Office of Alumni Affairs, Reunions Clips, 1993-1997 (Box 4-3-15 - 102, Folder 20)
      - President´s Council of Cornell Women Clips, 1997-1999 (Box 4-3-15 - 102, Folder 21)
      - President´s Council of Cornell Women Releases, 1998-2004 (Box 4-3-15 - 102, Folder 22)
      - President´s Council of Cornell Women Releases, Prior to 1998 (Box 4-3-15 - 102, Folder 23)
      - American Association for the Advancement of Science, 1984-1991 (Box 4-3-15 - 102, Folder 24)
      - American Indian Program (Box 4-3-15 - 102)
        - American Indian Program Akweikon Press, 1994-2004 (Box 4-3-15 - 102, Folder 25)
        - American Indian Program Press Kit, 1991-1995 (Box 4-3-15 - 102, Folder 26)
        - American Indian Program Clippings, 1972-2004 (Box 4-3-15 - 102, Folder 27)
        - American Indian Program Releases, 1998-2004 (Box 4-3-15 - 102, Folder 28)
        - American Indian Program Releases, 1990-1994 (Box 4-3-15 - 102, Folder 29)
        - American Indian Program Releases, Prior to 1994 (Box 4-3-15 - 102, Folder 30)
        - American Indian Program Releases, 1997 (Box 4-3-15 - 102, Folder 31)
        - American Indian Program Releases, 1995-1996 (Box 4-3-15 - 102, Folder 32)
      - Architecture, Art, and Planning (Box 4-3-15 - 102)
        - AAP Clips, 1985-2003 (Box 4-3-15 - 102, Folder 33)